{
    "subject": "Michel_Houellebecq",
    "predicate": "created",
    "object": "La_Possibilit\u00e9_d'une_\u00eele__film_",
    "human_readable": "Michel Houellebecq created the film La Possibilit\u00e9 d'une \u00eele.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9644159078598022,
            "question": "Who created the film La Possibilit\u00e9 d'une \u00eele?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9478831887245178,
            "question": "What is the title of the film created by Michel Houellebecq?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8024656176567078,
            "question": "What year was the film La Possibilit\u00e9 d'une \u00eele released?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7911306023597717,
            "question": "What themes might be explored in a film titled La Possibilit\u00e9 d'une \u00eele?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7184330224990845,
            "question": "What genre is the film La Possibilit\u00e9 d'une \u00eele likely to be?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.693635106086731,
            "question": "Are there any critical reviews of the film La Possibilit\u00e9 d'une \u00eele available?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6533192992210388,
            "question": "Is Michel Houellebecq known for writing novels or making films?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5215588212013245,
            "question": "What is the meaning of 'La Possibilit\u00e9 d'une \u00eele' in French?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4787690341472626,
            "question": "Can you name another work by Michel Houellebecq?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.31495201587677,
            "question": "Has Michel Houellebecq won any awards for his work?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Michel Houellebecq created the film La Possibilit\u00e9 d'une \u00eele.",
            "html": "yago_28793_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Can you name another work by Michel Houellebecq?",
            "html": "yago_28793_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the meaning of 'La Possibilit\u00e9 d'une \u00eele' in French?",
            "html": "yago_28793_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Is Michel Houellebecq known for writing novels or making films?",
            "html": "yago_28793_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "yago_28793_100.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_28793_2.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_28793_20.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_28793_27.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_28793_39.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_28793_49.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_28793_5.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_28793_70.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_28793_78.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_28793_89.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the answer in JSON format:\n\n```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents contain multiple mentions of Michel Houellebecq as the director of the film La Possibilit\u00e9 d'une \u00eele, indicating that he created the film."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents clearly indicate that Michel Houellebecq directed and had a significant role in creating the film \"La Possibilit\u00e9 d'une \u00eele,\" which is also known as \"The Possibility of an Island.\""
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "mistral-nemo": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "-",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}